joyofandroid.com 2019-06-09

# Privacy

At JoyofAndroid.com, the privacy of our visitors is our ultimate concern.  Because we want our visitors to be confident and comfortable in using our website and our services, we are executing appropriate processes and procedures to protect the personal information that you have shared with us. This Privacy Policy summarize the types of personal information that are received and collected as well as how it is used by JoyofAndroid.com

## Definition of Terms

This Privacy Policy Section identifies the words that Users will frequently run into while using our website JoyofAndroid.com

 **“JoyofAndroid”, “Joy of Android”, “We”, “Our”, “Us”** points to the entire management of JoyofAndroid.com.

 **“Site” or “Website”** refers to our website JoyofAndroid.com and the pages hosted by JoyofAndroid.com

 **“Guest”** is the term for an individual that browses the Website’s services without subscribes to our email list.

“ **Subscriber** ” is the term used for a user who subscribes to our email list through feed burner or any other email marketing software. ****

 **“User”** is a collective term for Subscriber, Member and Guest. ****

## Collection of Personal Information

The website collects visitor’s email through feed burner. If you have subscribed to our services we may use the information to send updates on the latest Android trends. The collected information includes but not limited to user’s name, email address, contact number and mailing address.

## Collection of Non-Personal Information:

### Advertising cookies:

JoyofAndroid.com uses wide range of third party tracking tools and advertisers. Like any other website, these third parties or advertisers may place cookies that can collect and send aggregate data. You should consult the respective privacy policies of the third party ad servers for more detailed information. JoyofAndroid.com does not control the activities of such advertisers. Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information. If you do not wish you to agree with this policy, you must leave the Site right now.

### Google Analytics Cookie

JoyofAndroid.com uses Google Analytics as web analytics tool. Google Analytics cookie is used to optimize, inform and collect data about the traffic on this Site.

### Alexa Scripts Cookie

Alexa scripts used for tracking the number of visitors of the JoyofAndroid.com may place a Cookie. Aggregate data are collected, transmitted, stored and analyzed to check our web traffic.

## How Collected Information are Used:

JoyofAndroid.com gathers and makes use of a User’s information to attain the following:

  * Outstanding Customer Service
  * Timely updates
  * Personalized advertisement
  * Improve user experience

We may contact you when one of the below events happen:

  1. When you subscribe to your email list through feedburner or any other email list.
  2. When you comment on our blog post and subscribe to be noted by email on follow up comments or leave a comment that needs direct reply to you.
  3. When you contact us for any information through our contact us form.
  4. When you leave offline message to one of our chat windows and ask us to contact you.

## External Link & Affiliate Commission Policy

From time to time, JoyofAndroid.com may link to external websites which might be helpful for the user. We may receive monetary benefits by referring products, apps and websites. However JoyofAndroid.com does not control the content available on the third party websites.

## Copyright Policy

All content – texts, media files, images and videos are copyright to the owners of JoyofAndroid.com. You may not copy, or reproduce it online or in offline without the written permission of the owners. Such behavior will call for DMCA take down and legal actions if necessary.

JoyofAndroid.com reserves the right to update or modify the Privacy Policy whenever it is deemed to be necessary. We will post a notification on our site and update the date at the bottom of this page. If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy policy, you can fill up and submit the form located at <https://joyofandroid.com/contact-us/>.

JOA uses a number of Ad partners and affiliates to monetise our site. A user agrees that they consent to privacy policy of our ad partners. An example ad partner privacy policy is available [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/joyofandroid.com).

 **This document was last updated on September  26, 2018**
